

Mads Engberg

mads.engberg@hotmail.com

+45 51 72 19 33

I am a kind and patient person who loves honest teamwork and knowledge sharing. I have a background in teaching and pedagogy.

I especially adore the part of game development that lies in the limbo

between technology and design. The place where the gameplay mechanics, the game feel and the user experience is created. Even if my academic background is mostly technical, I have large interest in, and respect for, the creative side of game-making.

Skills

Core programming languages: C++, C# Unity, Java, GLSL Other programming languages: C, C# .NET, F#, HTML5, JavaScript, Matlab

Portfolio

https://www.itu.dk/people/engb/

Experience

Danish Technical University / Teaching Assistant in course "02121 Introduction to Software Technology" under Carsten Witt.

September 2015 - January 2016, DTU Compute

Furesø Municipality / Pedagogue for a child with special requirements (unnamed illness)

August 2011 - July 2013

Voluntary Work / Organiser for Level One: Jam! A new game jam at ITU.

December 2017 - PRESENT, ITU

Voluntary Work / Organiser for game jam meet-up at KADK in lieu with Ludum Dare 40.

October 2017 - December 2017, KADK

Education

IT-University of Copenhagen / MSc in Games Technology

August 2017 - PRESENT, ITU

Danish Technical University / BSc in Software Technology

August 2014 - July 2017, DTU